[{"body": [{"type": "select-divide", "title": "解决问题", "unit": "个", "name": "桃子", "unit2": "只", "name2": "猴子", "stem": "他们能分到同样多的", "animal": {"img": "animal_monkey/793fc4b39c09915005e03c0a5974abf4.svg", "num": 2}, "thing": {"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 2}}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "2", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-7-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "select-divide", "title": "解决问题", "unit": "个", "name": "桃子", "unit2": "只", "name2": "猴子", "stem": "他们能分到同样多的", "animal": {"img": "animal_monkey/793fc4b39c09915005e03c0a5974abf4.svg", "num": 2}, "thing": {"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 3}}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "2", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-7-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "select-divide", "title": "解决问题", "unit": "个", "name": "桃子", "unit2": "只", "name2": "猴子", "stem": "他们能分到同样多的", "animal": {"img": "animal_monkey/793fc4b39c09915005e03c0a5974abf4.svg", "num": 2}, "thing": {"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 4}}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "2", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-7-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "select-divide", "title": "解决问题", "unit": "个", "name": "桃子", "unit2": "只", "name2": "猴子", "stem": "他们能分到同样多的", "animal": {"img": "animal_monkey/793fc4b39c09915005e03c0a5974abf4.svg", "num": 2}, "thing": {"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 5}}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "2", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-7-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "select-divide", "title": "解决问题", "unit": "个", "name": "桃子", "unit2": "只", "name2": "猴子", "stem": "他们能分到同样多的", "animal": {"img": "animal_monkey/793fc4b39c09915005e03c0a5974abf4.svg", "num": 3}, "thing": {"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 3}}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "2", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-7-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "select-divide", "title": "解决问题", "unit": "个", "name": "桃子", "unit2": "只", "name2": "猴子", "stem": "他们能分到同样多的", "animal": {"img": "animal_monkey/793fc4b39c09915005e03c0a5974abf4.svg", "num": 3}, "thing": {"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 4}}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "2", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-7-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "select-divide", "title": "解决问题", "unit": "个", "name": "桃子", "unit2": "只", "name2": "猴子", "stem": "他们能分到同样多的", "animal": {"img": "animal_monkey/793fc4b39c09915005e03c0a5974abf4.svg", "num": 3}, "thing": {"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 5}}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "2", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-7-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "select-divide", "title": "解决问题", "unit": "个", "name": "桃子", "unit2": "只", "name2": "猴子", "stem": "他们能分到同样多的", "animal": {"img": "animal_monkey/793fc4b39c09915005e03c0a5974abf4.svg", "num": 4}, "thing": {"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 4}}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "2", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-7-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "select-divide", "title": "解决问题", "unit": "个", "name": "桃子", "unit2": "只", "name2": "猴子", "stem": "他们能分到同样多的", "animal": {"img": "animal_monkey/793fc4b39c09915005e03c0a5974abf4.svg", "num": 4}, "thing": {"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 5}}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "2", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-7-03"}, {"body": [{"type": "select-divide", "title": "解决问题", "unit": "个", "name": "桃子", "unit2": "只", "name2": "猴子", "stem": "他们能分到同样多的", "animal": {"img": "animal_monkey/793fc4b39c09915005e03c0a5974abf4.svg", "num": 5}, "thing": {"imgItem": ["tableware_plate/6e3aab481345454d985eb3169d703e2a.svg", "fruits/8afcdefaeb0f5edf4f1d45ec4b0acbd7.svg"], "num": 5}}], "answers": [0], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "2", "type": "选择", "number": "1-1-7-03"}]